Guide to the Andrew F. Smith Collection of Cookery Ephemera MSS.295
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Cookery Ephemera, 1798-2009
  - The Best Foods, Inc.--CPC International, Inc.; Richard Hellmann, Inc.--General Foods Corporation, 1927-1967 (Box 3, Folder 14-15)
    Best Foods, Inc. Three Meals a Day –with NUCOA. New York, NY: Best Foods Inc., 1930.
    Best Foods, a Division of CPC International. Fresh Ideas for Fruits & Vegetables; 24 Recipes Plus Buying and Handling Hints. Place of publication unknown: Best Foods, a Division of CPC International, undated.
    Hellmann. Richard Hellmann's Blue Ribbon Mayonnaise. New York, NY: Richard Hellmann, Inc., 1927
  - Better Homes and Gardens, 1948, circa 1970s (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Better Homes. 50 All-Time Great Hamburger Recipes. Place of publication unknown: Better Homes and Gardens, undated.
  - Bewley Mills, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Bewley Mills. Bewley's Best Bakes Better Bread, Biscuit, Pastry, Cake A Few Cooking Suggestions. Ft. Worth, TX: Bewley Mills, undated.
  - Birrell & Garnett, Ltd., circa 1930s (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - The Blanton Company--Creamo Margarin, circa 1930s (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Blanton Company. "Creamo is a Distinctive Product 31 Years' Experience Behind It." St. Louis, MO: Blandon Co., undated.
  - Blitzruhrschussel Und Amerikaner-Quirltopf--Stable & Friedel Stuggart, circa 1900 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Blue Moon Foods, Inc.; Bohack Food Markets, circa 1960s (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Blue Moon Foods, Inc. Louis, Elsa Wallin. Blue Moon Recipes Cheese Spreads, Vitamized and Pasturized Gold-N-Rich Cheese. Thorp, WI: Blue Moon Foods, Inc., undated.
  - The Borden Company--Eagle Brand; Comstock Foods, 1942-1969 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Borden. This is My Book of Magic Recipes. Made with Borden's Eagle Brand Sweetened Condensed Milk. New York, NY: The Borden Company, 1942.
    Borden. 50 New Food Ideas that Start with Borden's Wej-cut Cream Cheese. New York, NY: Borden Co., undated.
    Borden. 21 "None Such" Mince Meat Recipes. New York, NY: Borden Co., 1952.
    Borden. Elsie's Hostess Recipe Book using Borden. New York, NY: Borden Co., undated.
    Borden. The Dessert Lovers' Handbook; Eagle Brand Sweetened Condensed Milk. New York, NY: Borden Co., 1973.
    Borden, Comstock Foods. Homemade Desserts Quick n' Easy Comstock Fillings. Newark, NY [sic]: Comstock Foods, Division of the Borden Company, undated.
  - Borden's Condensed Milk Company, 1909-1929 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Borden. Feeding the Baby in Summer. New York, NY: The Borden Company, 1929.
    Borden. Borden's Eagle Brand Book of Recipes. New York, NY: Borden's Condensed Milk Company, undated.
    Borden. Borden's Recipes. New York: Borden's Condensed Milk Co., undated.
    Borden. New Magic in the Kitchen. New York, NY: Borden's Condensed Milk Co., undated.
    Borden. Recipes The Borden Way. New York, NY: Borden's Condensed Milk Co., undated. circa 1909.
  - Borg-Warner Corporation--Norge Division, circa 1950s (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Norge Division, Borg-Warner Corporation. Norge Recipe Book. Detroit, MI: Norge Division, Borg-Warner Corporation, undated.
    Norge Division, Borg-Warner Corporation. Norge Cold Cookery and Recipe Digest. Detroit, MI: Norge Division, Borg-Warner Corporation, undated.
  - Bosman & Lohman Company--Nut-Let Peanut Butter, circa 1914 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Bosman & Lohman Co. The Story of Nut-Let Peanut Butter; From the Vine to the Table. Norfolk, VA: Bosman & Lohman, circa 1914.
  - Boston Branch Tea & Grocery House, 1879 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Boston Branch. The Housekeeper's Friend Containing Valuable Receipts. Hartford, CT: Boston Branch Tea and Grocery House, 1879.
  - Boston Chamber of Commerce; The Boston Cooking School Magazine Company, 1891-1920s (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Boston Produce Exchange; Boston Produce Market, 1884 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Boston Woven Hose & Rubber Company; The Bowker Company, 1890, 1919, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Boston Woven Hose & Rubber Co. Cold Pack Canning. Cambridge, MA: Boston Woven Hose & Rubber Co., 1919.
    Boston Woven Hose & Rubber Co. Home Canners' Text Book. Cambridge, MA: Boston Woven Hose & Rubber Co., 1936.
  - Bostwick, Lucy W., 1883 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Braeder, Janice W.; Brazil Nut Association, circa 1950s-1980s (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Brazil Nut Association. A Parade of Brazil Nut Recipes. New York, NY: Brazil Nut Association, undated.
  - Bread, Flour, and Yeast Research, 1861-1990s (Box 4, Folder 14-15)
    Hulman and Company. Clabber Girl Baking Book. Terre Haute, IN: Hulman and Company, undated.
    R. B. Davis. Lesson Plan on Christmas Suggestions. Hoboken, NJ: R. B. Davis Company, 1931.
  - Brer Rabbit; Breuker & Kessler Company Philadelphia--E. H. Jacob, circa 1900s (Box 4, Folder 16)
    E. H. Jacob. "Jacob's Hothouse Mushrooms." Westchester, PA: E. H. Jacob, undated.
  - Brick Church Recipes, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Briggs, F. M., 1916-1920 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Brotherhood Wine Company; Brown-Blodgett Company, 1890-circa 1920s (Box 4, Folder 19)
    Brown-Blodgett Co. Ice Cream Delightful Ways to Serve It. St. Paul, MN: Brown-Blodgett Co., undated.
  - Browning, W. A., 1873 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - The Buffalo Commercial, Uneeda Biscuits and Royal Baking Powder, 1903 (Box Shared Fales 001, Folder 7)
  - Bullard & Foster, Druggists, 1887 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Bullard & Foster, Druggists. The Housekeepers Friend. Keene, NH: Bullard & Foster, Druggists, 1887.
  - Burnham & Morrill Company, circa 1910, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Burnham and Morrill Co. Hill, Janet McKenzie. Good Eating. Portland, ME: Burnham and Morrill Co., circa 1910.
    Burnham & Morrill Co. Sea Foods and Vegetables; Baked Beans and Brown Bread. Portland, ME: Burnham & Morrill Co., undated.
  - Burns, J. H., circa 1850s (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Burpee Can Sealer Company, circa 1920s (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Burpee Can Sealer Co. The Modern Way of Canning with the Burpee Home Can Sealer; Recipes for Fruits Vegetables Soups Meats Fish. Fourth edition. Chicago, IL: Burpee Can Sealer Co., undated.
  - The Burt Olney Canning Company--New York Canners, Inc., 1905-1922 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Olney Canning Co. Burt Olney's Soups, Salads and Desserts. Oneida, NY: The Burt Olney Canning Company, 1905.
    Olney Canning Co. Burt Olney's Soups, Salads and Desserts. Eighth Edition. Oneida, NY: The Burt Olney Canning Company, 1910.
    Olney Canning Co. Burt Olney's Soups, Salads and Desserts. Fourteenth Edition. Oneida, NY: The Burt Olney Canning Company, 1922.
  - Butter Improvement Company, 1879 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Butter Improvement Co. Hints to Butter-Makers; Book of Reference for the Farmer and Husbandman. Buffalo: Butter Improvement Co., 1879.
  - Cadbury, circa 1900s (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - C. A. Durr Packing Company, Inc.; Caixa De Pontevedra, 1925, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    C. A. Durr Packing Co. Durr's Mohawk Valley Food Hints. Utica, NY: C. A. Durr Packing Co., 1925.
  - Calavo Growers of California, 1927-1949 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Calavo Growers of California. California Presents CALAVO The Aristocrat of the Salad Fruits. Los Angeles, CA: Calavo Growers of California, undated.
    Calavo Growers of California. CALAVO Aristocrat of Avocados. Los Angeles, CA: Calavo Growers of California, undated.
    Calavo Growers of California. Introducing the Calavo. Los Angeles, CA: Calavo Growers of California, 1927.
    Calavo Growers of California. The Calavo Hostess Book. Los Angeles, CA: Calavo Growers of California, undated.
    Calavo Growers of California. The Calavo Book of Popular Avocado Recipes. Los Angeles, CA: Calavo Growers of California, 1949.
  - California Annual State Fair; California Avocado Advisory Board, 1929, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    California Avocado Advisory Board. The Avocado Bravo. Revised Edition. Newport Beach, CA: California Avocado Advisory Board, circa 1976.
  - California Associated Raisin Company; Sun-Maid Raisin Growers of California; Sunland Sales Cooperative Association, 1914-1925 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    California Associated Raisin Co. Souvenir California Raisin Recipe Book. Fresno, CA: California Associated Raisin Co., 1914.
    California Associated Raisin Co. Sun-Maid Raisins Their Food Value and 92 Selected Recipes. Fresno, CA: California Associated Raisin Co., 1921.
    Sunland Sales Cooperative Association. The Story of Dried Fruit. Place of publication unknown: Sunland Sales Cooperative Association, undated.
    Sun-Maid Raisin Growers of California. Downright Delicious Sun-Maid Raisin Recipes. Fresno: Sun-Maid Raisin Growers of California, undated.
    Sun-Maid Raisin Growers of California. Bradley, Alice; Belle De Graf; Sarah Field Splint; and Caroline B. King. Famous Cooks' Recipes for Raisin Cookery. Fresno, CA: Sun-Maid Raisin Growers of California, 1925.
  - California Canning Peach Industry; California Dried Fruit Research Institute, circa 1960-1970s (Box 5, Folder 12)
    California Canning Peach Industry. California Canned Peach Recipe Book. San Francisco, CA: California Canning Peach Industry, undated.
    California Dried Fruit Research Institute. The Story of Dried Fruit. San Francisco, CA: California Dried Fruit Research Institute, undated.
  - California Fruit Growers Exchange-- Sunkist Bulletin, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Scope and Contents
    California Fruit Growers Exchange. Everyday Recipes for Oranges & Lemons. Los Angeles, CA: California Fruit Growers Exchange, undated.
    California Fruit Growers Exchange. Recipes for Every Day for Oranges and Lemons. Los Angeles, CA: California Fruit Growers Exchange, undated.
    California Fruit Growers Exchange. "Entertaining with Fruit." Sunkist Bulletin #4. Los Angeles, CA: Education Division, California Fruit Growers Exchange, 1941.
    California Fruit Growers Exchange. Sunkist Bulletin. Place of publication unknown: Domestic Science Lesson 12, 15, 17, 19, 28, 29.
  - California Fruit Growers Exchange--Sunkist Educational Exhibit, circa 1926 (Box Shared Fales 003, Folder 1)
    California Fruit Growers Exchange. Sunkist Educational Exhibit. Los Angeles, CA: California Fruit Growers Exchange, undated. circa 1920s.
  - California Fruit Growers Exchange--Sunkist Lemons & Oranges, 1911-1940 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    California Fruit Growers Exchange. Recipes for Dainty Dishes, Culinary, Toilet & Medicinal Hints. "Sunkist" Lemons: Their Many Uses as a Household Toilet & Medicinal Necessity. Chicago, IL: California Fruit Growers Exchange, undated.
    California Fruit Growers Exchange. Sunkist Lemons Bring Out the Flavor. Los Angeles, CA: California Fruit Growers Exchange, 1938.
    California Fruit Growers Exchange. Sunkist Lemons Bring Out the Flavor. Los Angeles, CA: California Fruit Growers Exchange, 1939.
    California Fruit Growers Exchange. Sunkist Orange Recipes for Year-round Freshness. Los Angeles, CA: California Fruit Growers Exchange, 1940.
    California Fruit Growers Exchange. Feeding the Child for Health with Menus and Recipes for the Diet of Mother and Child. 5th edition. Los Angeles, CA: California Fruit Growers Exchange, 1931.
    Exchange Orange Products Co. Pure Concentrated Orange Juice; What it is; How to Use It. San Dimas, CA: Exchange Orange Products Co., undated.
    Mutual Orange Distributors. Zestful Recipes for Every Meal; Pure Gold and Silver Seal; Oranges-Lemons Grapefruit. Redlands: Mutual Orange Distributors, undated.
  - California Fruit Growers Exchange-- Sunkist Recipes: Oranges-Lemons, 1916 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    California Fruit Growers Exchange with Miss Alice Bradley. Sunkist Recipes: Oranges-Lemons. Los Angeles, CA: California Fruit Growers Exchange, 1916.
  - California Home Economics Association--Southern Section, 1920-1928 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    California Home Economics Association. Pastries and Desserts. Los Angeles, CA: California Home Economics Association, 1921.
  - California Lima Bean Growers Association; California Prune & Apricot Growers Association, 1947-1950 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    California Prune & Apricot Growers Association. Sunsweet. San Jose, CA: California Prune & Apricot Growers Association, 1947.
    California Prune & Apricot Growers Association. Sunsweet Recipes. San Jose, CA: California Prune & Apricot Growers Association, 1950.
  - California Perfume Company, Inc., circa 1886 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - California Walnut Growers Association; California Wine Advisory Board, 1938-1966 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    California Walnut Growers Association. To Win New Cooking Fame Just Add Walnuts. Los Angeles, CA: California Walnut Growers Association, circa 1937.
    California Walnut Growers Association. Around the Kitchen Clock with Walnuts. Los Angeles, CA: California Walnut Growers Association, undated.
    California Walnut Growers Association. Parker, Marian Jane. Menu Magic in a Nutshell. Los Angeles, CA: California Walnut Growers Association, circa 1950.
  - Calumet Baking Powder Company, circa 1900-1920s (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Calumet Baking Powder Co. Parker, Marian Jane. Cream of Tartar and Tartaric Acid. Chicago, IL: Calumet Baking Powder Co., undated.
    Calumet Baking Powder Co. Reliable Recipes. Place of publication unknown: Calumet Baking Powder Co., undated.
    Calumet Baking Powder Co. Reliable Recipes. Polskie Wydanie. Chicago, IL: Calumet Baking Powder Co., undated.
    Calumet Baking Powder Co. Calumet Cook Book. Chicago, IL: Calumet Baking Powder Co., undated.
  - Calumet Baking Powder Company, 1931 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    The Calumet Baking Book; Reliable Recipes
  - Canada Department of Agriculture, 1926-1969 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Canadian National Railways; Canadian Living Magazine; The Dairy Bureau of Canada; FC's Party Guide; Atlantic Insight, 1984-1987 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Canapé Parade; Canned Salmon Industry, 1932, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Canapé Parade. Canapé Parade; 100 Hors D'Oeuvre Recipes. Scarborough, NY: Canapé Parade, 1932.
    Canned Salmon Industry. Magic Entrees to Make with Canned Salmon. Seattle, WA: Canned Salmon Industry, 1937.
  - Cape Elizabeth Grange Cook Book, circa 1900-1920s (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Cape Elizabeth Grange. Cook Book. Cape Elizabeth, ME: Cape Elizabeth Grange, undated.
  - The Capital City Products Company--Dixie Vegetable Oleomargarine; Card Seed Company, circa 1920-1940s (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Capital City Products Co. Blake, Mary. Dixie Margarine Kitchen Tested Recipes. Columbus, OH: Capital City Products Co., undated.
  - Carnation Brand Flour--Voigt Milling Company, undated (Box Shared Fales 002, Folder 4)
  - Carnation Company--Carnation Milk Products; Contadina Foods, Inc.; Castle & Cooke, Inc.--Dole Company, 1931-1965, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Carnation Company. Blake, Mary. Carnation's Family Favorites. Los Angeles, CA: Carnation Company, 1956.
    Carnation Company. Blake, Mary. Frozen Salads and Desserts. Milwaukee, WI: Carnation Company, undated.
    Carnation Milk Products Company. Blake, Mary. A Few of My Favorite Recipes. Oconomowoc, WI: The Carnation Company, undated.
    Contadina Foods, Inc. How to Be Worldly without Leaving Your Kitchen. Los Angeles, CA: Contadina Foods, Inc., a subsidiary of Carnation, 1970.
    Dole Company. The Pineapple Cookbook. Honolulu, HI: Dole Company, undated.
  - Cassell & Company, Ltd., undated (Box Shared Fales 002, Folder 5)
  - C. D. Mills, 1904 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Mills' Genuine Home-Made Bread. Mills' Genuine Home-made Bread. Brooklyn: Mills' Genuine Home-Made Bread, circa 1904.
  - C. E. Cocks & Sons, 1894 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    C. E. Cocks & Sons. The Art of Cookery and Rules of Propriety. New York, NY: New York Publishing, 1894.
  - The Centaur Company, 1881 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Centaur. New York Receipt Book. New York, NY: The Centaur Company, 1881.
  - Central Hudson Gas & Electric Company; Central Oil and Gas Stove Company; Central Manufacturing Company, 1900-1914 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Central Oil and Gas Stove Co. The Florence Automatic Household Helper. Gardiner, MA: Central Oil and Gas Stove Co., undated.
  - The Cerealine Manufacturing Company, 1886, 1888 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Cerealine Manufacturing Co. Cereal Foods. Columbus, IN: Cerealine Manufacturing Co., 1886.
    Cerealine Manufacturing Co. New Cook Book for Cerealine Flakes. Columbus, IN: Cerealine Manufacturing Co., 1888.
  - C. F. Mueller Company, 1920, 1923 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    C. F. Mueller Co. Mueller's Tomato and Cheese Recipes. Jersey City, NJ: C. F. Mueller Co., 1920.
    C. F. Mueller Co. From the Heart of the Wheat. Jersey City, NJ: C. F. Mueller Co., 1923.
  - C. F. Sauer Company, circa 1900-1920s (Box 6, Folder 16)
    C. F. Sauer Company. Fifty Recipes on Flavoring by a Famous New York Chef. Richmond, VA: C. F. Sauer Company, circa 1920.
    C. F. Sauer Co. Choice Recipes Sauer's Famous Flavoring Extracts; Imparts That True Fruit Flavor. Richmond, VA: C. F. Sauer Co., undated.
  - Chamberlaine Medicine Company; Charette Drug Company, 1908 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Chamberlain Medicine Co. Welch, Mary B. Choice Recipes for Cakes Pies Puddings Creams. Des Moines, IA: Chamberlain Medicine Co., 1908.
    Charette Drug Co. Chafing Dish Recipes; also Deserts and Candy Making. Goldfield, NV: Charette Drug Co., undated.
  - Charles A. King, Pure Food Department; Chas. Arbuckle & Company, 1884, 1896 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    King. And Cupid. Boston, MA: Pure Food Department, Charles A. King, 1896.
  - Charles B. Knox Gelatine Company, Inc., 1896-1960 (Box 6, Folder 19, Box 7, Folder 1-2)
    Knox. Dainty Dishes Made of Knox Gelatine. Johnstown, NY: Charles B. Knox Co., 1910.
    Knox. Dainty Desserts for Dainty People Knox Gelatine. Johnstown, NY: Charles B. Knox Gelatine Co., 1896.
    Knox. Markward, Rose. Dainty Desserts for Dainty People. Eighth edition. Johnstown, NY: C. B. Knox, circa 1901.
    Knox. Knox Gelatine; Dainty Desserts, Salads, Candies. Johnston, NY: Charles B. Knox Gelatine Co., 1927.
    Knox. Knox Gelatine; Dainty Desserts, Candies Salads. Johnstown, NY: Charles B. Knox Co., 1931.
    Knox. Knox Gelatine; Desserts, Salads, Candies and Frozen Dishes. Johnstown, NY: Charles B. Knox Co., 1936.
    Knox. How to Reduce and Stay Reduced. Johnstown, NY: Charles B. Knox Co., 1955.
  - Charles Gulden, Inc.; Charles E. Hires Company, circa 1920s-1940s (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Hires. The Animals Trip to Town. "Hires' Household Extract for Making Root Beer. Place of publication unknown: publisher unknown, undated.
  - Chase & Sanborn, 1893-1910 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Chase & Sanborn, Tea & Coffee Importers. A Picture Story of Tea and Coffee. Boston and New York: Barta Press,, circa 1910.
    Chase & Sanborn. Coffee Dainties Made with Chase and Sanborn's "Seal Brand Coffee. Camden, NJ: W. J. Stoddard, undated.
  - Chase, A.W., 1958 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Chattanooga Medicine Company, circa 1900 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Chattanooga Medicine Co. The Cardui Cook Book. Chattanooga, TN: Chattanooga Medicine Co., circa 1900.
  - Chef Murre Paul; Chester Kent & Company, circa 1900, 1970s (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Chester Kent & Co. McBirney, Nettie. Recipes for Desserts. Boston, MA: Chester Kent & Co., undated.
  - Chicago Dietetic Supply House, Inc., 1930 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Christian Hansen's; D. H. Burrell & Co.; Burrell & Whitman, undated (Box Shared Fales 002, Folder 6)
  - Christian D.A. Hansen's Laboratory, Inc.--Junket, 1930-1935 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Hansen's Laboratory, Inc. Directions. Little Falls, NY: The Junket Folks, Chr. Hansen's Laboratory, Inc., undated.
    Hansen's Laboratory, Inc. Junket Desserts and Ice Cream. Little Falls, NY: The Junket Folks, Chr. Hansen's Laboratory, Inc., undated.
    Hansen's Laboratory, Inc. The Junket Book; Delicious Digestible Desserts and Ice Cream. Second edition. Little Falls, NY: The Junket Folks, Chr. Hansen's Laboratory, Inc., 1935.
    Hansen's Laboratory, Inc. Mason, Mary. How to Make Delicious Rennet-Custards and Smooth Ice Cream. Little Falls, NY: The Junket Folks, Chr. Hansen's Laboratory, Inc., 1936.
    Junket Brand Foods. Fudge Fancies. Little Falls, NY: Junket Brand Foods, undated.
  - C.H. Stuart & Company, 1908 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Stuart. Stuart's Cook Book Choice Original and Selected Practical Recipes. New York, NY: C. H. Stuart & Co., 1908.
  - Church & Company--Arm & Hammer; Church & Dwight Company, 1896-1908 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Church & Co. Book of Valuable Receipts. Twenty-sixth Edition of One Million Each. New York, NY: Arm & Hammer, circa 1896.
    Church & Co. Book of Valuable Receipts. Thirtieth Edition of One Million Each. New York, NY: Arm & Hammer, circa 1900.
    Church & Co. Book of Valuable Receipts. 34th edition of One Million Each. New York, NY: Arm & Hammer, circa 1900.
    Church & Dwight. Arm & Hammer Bicarbonate of Soda Book of Valuable Recipes. 65th edition. New York, NY: Church & Dwight Co., circa 1915.
  - Church & Dwight Company, Inc.--Arm & Hammer, 1900-1925 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Church & Co. Book of Valuable Receipts. 44th edition of One Million Each. New York, NY: Arm & Hammer, circa 1900.
    Church & Dwight. Arm & Hammer Bicarbonate of Soda Book of Valuable Recipes. 66th edition. New York, NY: Church & Dwight Co., circa 1915.
    Church & Dwight. Arm & Hammer Baking Soda Bicarbonate of Soda Book of Valuable Recipes. 75th edition. New York, NY: Church & Dwight Co., undated.
    Church & Dwight. The Great Arm & Hammer Almanac 1915. New York, NY: Church & Dwight Company, 1915.
    Church & Dwight. Arm & Hammer Almanac 1921. New York, NY: Church & Dwight Company, 1921.
    Church & Dwight. Arm & Hammer Almanac 1922. New York, NY: Church & Dwight Company, 1922.
    Church & Dwight. A Friend in Need; Facts Worth Knowing about Arm & Hammer Baking Soda. New York, NY: Church & Dwight, 1925.
  - Church & Dwight Company, Inc., 1913-1959 (Box 8, Folder 1, Box 7, Folder 13-15)
    Church & Dwight Co. Cow Brand Soda Cook Book and Facts Worth Knowing. New York, NY: Arm & Hammer, circa 1913.
    Church & Dwight. Anderson, Martha Lee. New-Fashioned Old-Fashioned Recipes. New York, NY: Church & Dwight Company, Inc., 1948.
    Church & Dwight. The Soda Almanac of Household Uses. Dublin, NH: The Old Farmer's Almanac, 1959.
    Church & Dwight. Recipes to Stretch Your Sugar Ration. New York, NY: Church & Dwight Co., 1942.
    Church & Dwight Co. Cow Brand Soda Cook Book and Facts Worth Knowing. New York, NY: Arm & Hammer, circa 1919.
    Church & Dwight. Anderson, Martha Lee, comp. Good Things to Eat. 77th edition. New York, NY: Church & Dwight, 1933.
    Church & Dwight. Anderson, Martha Lee, comp. Good Things to Eat. Montreal: Church & Dwight, Limited, 1933.
    Church & Dwight. Anderson, Martha Lee, comp. Good Things to Eat. 105th edition. New York, NY: Church & Dwight, 1933.
    Church & Dwight. Anderson, Martha Lee, comp. Good Things to Eat. 107th edition. New York, NY: Church & Dwight, 1933.
    Church & Dwight. Anderson, Martha Lee, comp. Good Things to Eat. 111th edition. New York, NY: Church & Dwight, 1935.
    Church & Dwight. Anderson, Martha Lee, comp. Good Things to Eat. 116th Edition. New York, NY: Church & Dwight, 1935.
    Church & Dwight. Anderson, Martha Lee, comp. Good Things to Eat. 117th Edition. New York, NY: Church & Dwight, 1936.
    Church & Dwight. Anderson, Martha Lee, comp. Good Things to Eat. New York, NY: Church & Dwight, 1938.
    Church & Dwight. Anderson, Martha Lee. Good Things to Eat. NY: Church & Dwight Co., Inc. 1938.
    Church & Dwight. Anderson, Martha Lee. Good Things to Eat. NY: Church & Dwight Co., Inc. 1957.
    Church & Dwight. Anderson, Martha Lee. Successful Baking for Flavor and Texture. New York, NY: Church & Dwight Company, Inc., 1933.
    Church & Dwight. Anderson, Martha Lee. Successful Baking for Flavor and Texture. 2nd edition. New York, NY: Church & Dwight Company, Inc., 1934.